A sound soul, dwells within a sound mind, and a sound body.
So, so this is... the Holy Sword Excalibur.
Victory and glory. I could become a famous hero.
With this legendary sword as a partner, even someone like me could achieve everlasting renown and magnificence.
It's decided! I'm going after the Holy Sword Excalibur!
Sorry, sorry.
I'm falling down to my shadow.
So, so Undo.
I'll cry out.
And I've won the only boyfriend for my head...
I am releasing fashnritt.
A life that makes it look like Osh.,
Or while the Lord adds head to the heart.
To be altered by making a wishin' this world.
I just love you!
I'll see you next time.
Why are you asking me?
Please, dude.
This is something only you can do.
We're counting on you, man.
Seriously.
It's something that only I can do?
Leave it to me!
Hey!
Don't forget about us!
Yeah, we're parched.
We could really use a couple sodas.
It's something else only you can do, Hiro.
Thank you!
Hmm.
Yo, Hiro!
Huh?
Come here a sec.
Okay, what is it, Blackstar?
The usual.
I need you for practice.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
I'm gonna die!
Do you think this move hurts enough?
My body doesn't mess and control like this!
Is it difficult to get out of?
My eyeballs are gonna pop out of my head!
Ow, ow, ow!
He could still use some more practice.
Hiro's kind of misnamed, isn't he?
He's a regular student like the rest of us.
He's just an ordinary guy.
You could use a lesson or two on how to be cool, man.
Damn.
Reaching the Holy Sword's the only chance I've got.
It's time to say farewell to the Academy's favorite errand boy.
I shall be transformed!
The Legend of the Holy Sword III,
the Academy gang leader's tale?
I am the great Blackstar!
No one can stop me because I'm the invincible man!
I'm looking so cool while walking to school!
Right, Tsubaki?
Yeah!
Hey, what the?
Isn't it early for fighting?
Please.
What a pitiful bunch you are.
I have been reborn as a true hero.
Ordinary people like you don't stand a chance against me.
You mean that hero kid did this?
This Academy is nothing special.
Him again?
My legend is far more impressive
than anything that has happened at this school.
All students and Meisters must hear it.
Fool!
My legend dates back to the 12th century, you see.
It began on a midsummer day with the sun blazing overhead.
No, wait.
It was a blustery autumn day.
I was an unsavory fellow back when it all started, which was in the winter, as I recall.
I ran with a tough crowd.
All the hot babes fought over me that summer.
Yes.
Yes, that's right.
It was summer.
A scorching midsummer day.
I was a dangerous man at the time, and yet refined somehow.
Everyone thought so.
They still think so to this day.
Although maybe they didn't think so as much back then.
But they definitely said I was dangerous, I'm sure of it.
And I know I've always been refined, so they must have been thinking it.
Yes.
Yes, indeed.
Everyone thought and said and talked about how amazing I was.
I'm still amazing, of course, but no longer the bad boy that I was back then,
on that chill, frozen winter day.
I will continue the retelling of my legend.
But first, there will be a five-minute break.
Stand still and await my return.
Hold on, you freak!
What do you want?
The stated five-minute break hasn't passed yet.
Say, don't I know you?
Yeah, it was a really memorable...
You can't wait five minutes?
Fool.
Watch the stick, dude.
Did you see before, Blackstar?
My incredible strength?
I'm no longer the miserable loser I was.
The Holy Sword has changed all that.
I've been transformed into a powerful hero.
Getting your hands on a particular weapon doesn't necessarily change you at all.
Besides, what could possibly be worth having to put up with this cane-waving freak?
Oh, please.
The 1,000 provisions I must observe to be Excalibur's Meister are so easy to handle,
I could do it in my sleep.
It seems to me the real question is,
how come you weren't able to handle the Holy Sword?
You were a real idiot.
Damn, have you even gotten to the part about the five-hour storytelling parties yet?
Now that you mention it, my legend began on the same day as today.
A Tuesday or a Wednesday.
Or a Saturday, perhaps.
Either make up your mind or shut up.
No, it was on Monday.
Though I suppose it could have been a Tuesday or a Wednesday.
Thursday is a distinct possibility, or Friday, even.
Although Monday does sound right.
And Saturday is a lovely day to begin a legend.
Perhaps it was a Thursday.
Or Tuesday.
Maybe Wednesday or Friday.
There's always Monday, too.
And Saturday.
We can't forget Saturday.
No, no.
It was almost certainly on a...
Shut up or I'll kill you!
I can't take it anymore!
We fight, then?
A fight, huh?
I'd like a piece of that action.
I'd like to check out what this legendary sword can do.
Same here.
With that guy around, it's impossible to maintain one's sanity.
Look at this stupid alien!
Wanna fight?
Killick Rung.
Blackstar.
Death the Kid.
A battle between the three best fighters in the Academy and Excalibur.
A worthy matchup.
I'll be joining the fight as well so you can see my new abilities up close and personal.
Excalibur!
Victory and glory
are mine now.
He is somewhat intimidating.
When all is said and done, the three of you will be nothing more than a footnote.
In the legend of the Holy Sword Excalibur.
Shut up!
Don't you remember who you are, Hero?
Wouldn't dare talk like that!
My new name is Hero the Brave.
I am Hero the Brave!
Oh, yeah?
Well, take this!
Heaven strike!
Coney and the Brave!
Ah!
If you do not follow the light, no blow you strike will ever touch Hero the Brave.
What? Where is he?
With this, you will be defeated.
Last move, Hero the Atomic.
Awesome. All he had to do was name the technique and they were deep fried.
I don't even know what he did.
Hm. So guys, what do you think about the new me? Pretty powerful, aren't I?
And thus the DWMA was taken over by Hero, former failed Meister and total loser.
What will become of the Academy now?
You'll have to wait until after the break to find out.
This is the perfect example of my soon-to-be legendary powers. I've made it into the girls' locker room.
Go away!
No!
What now?
Aw, if you don't like it, you'll have to find a way to defeat me!
You dirty pervert!
Excalibur's not in his usual spot!
Yeah!
Everybody worships me now that I'm Hero the Brave.
The ecstasy and uncertainty of being the chosen one is overwhelming.
He talks an awful lot about being transformed and that sort of thing.
But all that's really changed is now he's a jackass.
It's Ox!
How can he do such an awful thing to my beloved Kim?!
Hero, you're a dead man!
What?
Calm down and take a breath, Ox.
Look at those two.
I wonder how much longer they'll be able to pull this off.
We have to remember this is Hero.
He's a perpetual failure.
He'll get tired of the thousand provisions and give up before too much longer.
You're getting scary, Ox.
The one thousand provisions of the Holy Sword Excalibur.
Number 22.
On a refreshing morning, start out with a refreshing greeting.
Hero, good morning!
And a very good morning to you, Excalibur.
Now let us begin another great day, shall we?
This day will never come again, so we should spend it together.
Let's enjoy!
I'll kill him!
Number 452.
Attendance at the five-hour storytelling party is absolutely mandatory.
Your 20s will be the great transitional period of your life.
It is a time of crossroads, of immense change, of incredible uncertainty.
Indeed, my 20s were such a period for me.
That was when I evolved from a no-good troublemaker to the legendary sword you see before you today.
Many men envied my hairstyle, you see, and formed a fringe group, a sort of cult, if you will, dedicated to the adoration of my daring hairstyle.
They met every week, or was it every day?
As you may have noticed, humans are very young, from the time they are born until some years later.
I, however, was born old and wise, and would often discuss abstract...
That is all!
Number 578.
The hero must never tell a lie.
So, what you're telling me is that you didn't see anything?
That's correct. I swear, sir, I didn't see anything.
I see. But perhaps you know something about someone who did see something.
No, I don't know anything about anybody who saw anything anywhere.
Is that so? This is a complicated case indeed.
You see, no one saw you see nothing.
So, how can we confirm that you don't know anything or anyone anywhere?
Holmes, have you discovered anything?
Yes, I believe I have a viable theory.
Indeed, what do you think?
This man is the culprit.
That's right.
This man is the brother of the girl who went missing ten years ago,
and the author of this terribly tragic tale of revenge and murder.
Wow, you figured it all out.
Hey, please don't throw things.
Number 202.
Only the grandest of toilets is acceptable.
It's grand, all right.
But did he have to put it here?
This was the only location with enough room.
Number 667.
You will praise Excalibur at all times.
Magnificent Excalibur.
Munificent Excalibur.
Magnanimous Excalibur.
Number 172.
Seek harmony.
Seek it thus.
First, a haircut.
No, stop, hold it!
Number 75.
Celebrate Excalibur's birthday in grand style.
When is your birthday?
Every day.
May!
Really?
Then I'll think of 365 ways to celebrate,
and each one will be better than the one before.
Hooray!
Number 602.
Meals will always be prepared with the freshest ingredients.
For today's special ingredient,
we will be using the always delectable Red King crab.
Oh, it looks simply delicious.
It is superb.
Let me tell you.
I want some Red King crab.
Yes, right away.
Seconds.
Gladly, sir.
Why?
Well done.
You have met the 1,000 provisions.
Thank you so much.
As a reward, I'll sing you a song.
Listen carefully.
Yay!
Excalibur.
From the United King.
I'm looking for him.
I'm going to California.
Excalibur.
Oh!
So nice when I got to be real again!
Excuse me, Lord Death.
What we discussed earlier.
Yes, sir. It's about the legendary Holy Sword Excalibur, sir.
The legendary Holy Sword Excalibur.
By wielding it, Hiro has become sort of a gang leader within the DWMA.
Being a gang leader means wearing steel-toed boots,
dressing horribly, and picking fights.
And also keeping one's followers happy.
A job often easier said than done.
Their current project is setting up a cheer squad.
Hold on a second.
Since when does the DWMA have a student gang?
I know. It's news to me, too.
And here I thought we were done with that sort of thing.
Students will always look for someone to lead them.
Excalibur, Excalibur, Excalibur, Excalibur.
You're amazing, Hiro.
We're forming all of those thousand tasks.
You have an incredible partner.
I am truly a man to be revered.
Everyone, look.
Behold my splendor.
Worship me.
Does he seem a little overconfident to you, Sol?
Well, in a way, I guess he has found his ideal partner.
No, Satan isn't so.
How could this happen to Hiro of all people?
It can't be true.
Stories begin and stories end.
Often we cannot predict the outcome of a particular tale.
For example, everyone thought the unique bond between Hiro and the Holy Sword would last forever.
They were wrong.
Today was a perfect day, huh?
Have you forgotten provision number 573?
Always walk three steps behind me.
Of course.
I'm sorry.
Now, on our way.
Only a sneezing fit.
Let's go.
Sneezing.
Yo, Hiro!
Huh?
Ah, good morning, Black Star.
Would you like a sandwich or a soda, maybe?
Huh?
That's odd.
Seems like you're back to your normal self again.
What happened to Excalibur?
Oh, yeah, that.
I put it back again.
Stupid sword.
I don't get it.
You guys were getting along so well, weren't you?
The sneezes.
Once you started those sneezing fits, there was no way to stop it.
Huh?
Sneezing's gross.
Spit and snot go flying.
It goes everywhere.
I can't stand it.
Seriously.
The damn thing would be better off dead.
That's what finally got to you?
Being transformed was nice while it lasted, I guess.
Hey, do you know of any other way to completely change a person?
Yeah.
There's obviously a better way.
Try to be like me.
I'm the man who'll surpass God.
Just watching me and doing like I do will transform you in no time.
Once you go Black Star, you'll never go back.
Ha ha ha!
Real helpful.
Maybe I'll just start with some weight training for now.
Welcome to the storytelling party.
We will begin with my personal history.
I shall recount my legend from its historic beginning.
By the way, this top ad of mine is lined with the finest quality English seaweed roll.
Lame!
We'll see you next time.
Let's Veronica!
We will need you to miss the dream.
We'll get you there.
We'll be here.
Lame!
体調を受け散らすノイズルーオンに嗅うのには無頑固
シダブ君で彼らにしていないぜさらかなところのハート
そう今日と同じアスなんとかねえぜオールビンクに爆走
溺た心臓奏でるビートをいってきてるたしかないかしぼ
私は失って、失って、移ろう時の中で人知れず涙した夜も
全ても、思いなって、全てが、ただ自分ですよさまだ
行けるはずだろう
穢れなく光が 闇を貫いて
この時が永遠だと 今命が叫んでる
この心の奥に いつも君が映るよ
守るべき真実を ただ抱いてゆけ
繰り返す毎日の 体並みに飲まれても
まだ夢から覚める 俺たちはここにいる
いつも聞こえてくる 仲間たちの声が
孤独を振り払うように
街の風の中 ただ行くしかないさ
信じた行き様を
ああああああああああ
わあああああああああああ
物語雪の一笑別に
おまずい一笑なら
笑抱引 맞거나行ったら
物語 LLC行ったり
高尚自分頭の中に入れる
энあれあ人気ależyと
genius of my character, but I assure you
there are others who do. On the next episode
of Soul Eater, Resonance Link,
play the melody of the souls.
Worry not, everyone. I shall
return. See you later.
You are so unbearably lame.